<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://actionnook.com/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://actionnook.com/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://actionnook.com/collections/dragon-ball-z.atom"/>
  <title>Action Nook</title>
  <updated>2025-09-09T10:57:55+05:30</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Action Nook</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8831905988782</id>
    <published>2025-09-09T10:57:55+05:30</published>
    <updated>2025-09-09T10:57:55+05:30</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://actionnook.com/products/104-cm-led-katana-sword-rechargeable-type-c-light-sword-collectible"/>
    <title>104 cm LED Katana Sword – Rechargeable Type-C Light Sword Collectible</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>Action Nook</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0687/7413/3934/files/28FC4028-507D-45F1-AE9E-E9865C62E592.jpg?v=1757395633"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Action Nook<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            1999.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Unleash the glow of battle with this 104 cm LED Katana Sword. Featuring a sleek black-and-red design with a bright LED blade, this rechargeable sword is perfect for cosplay, display, or anime-inspired collections. Powered by Type-C charging, it combines traditional katana style with modern LED technology for the ultimate collectible.</p>
<p>Features: <br>- Full length: 104 cm (life-size display sword) <br>- LED light blade with vibrant glow effect <br>- Rechargeable via Type-C (cable included) <br>- Durable design with detailed hilt and scabbard <br>- Perfect for cosplay, anime displays, or collectors</p>
<p>Add this LED Katana Sword to your collection today and bring the power of glowing steel to your display!</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8831905988782</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="INR">1999.00</s:price>
      <s:sku/>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8827863302318</id>
    <published>2025-09-05T12:06:38+05:30</published>
    <updated>2025-09-05T12:06:38+05:30</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://actionnook.com/products/16-cm-super-saiyan-goku-figurine-dragon-ball-z-collectible"/>
    <title>16 cm Super Saiyan Goku Figurine – Dragon Ball Z Collectible</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>Action Nook</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0687/7413/3934/files/B790FAF7-60CF-4203-8292-C9D3A7585AD6.jpg?v=1757054152"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Action Nook<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            439.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Power up your collection with this 16 cm Super Saiyan Goku figurine. Captured in an intense battle stance, Goku is sculpted with detailed muscles, spiky golden hair, and his iconic torn orange gi. A must-have piece for any Dragon Ball Z fan who wants to bring the energy of the series to life.</p>
<p>Features: <br>- Size: 16 cm (dynamic mid-size figure) <br>- Detailed sculpt with vibrant colors <br>- Classic Super Saiyan design with golden hair <br>- Intense battle stance for an action-packed display <br>- Perfect gift for Dragon Ball fans and anime collectors</p>
<p>Add Super Saiyan Goku to your shelf today and feel the power of Dragon Ball Z in your collection!</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8827863302318</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="INR">439.00</s:price>
      <s:sku/>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8826868826286</id>
    <published>2025-09-04T21:02:00+05:30</published>
    <updated>2025-09-04T21:02:00+05:30</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://actionnook.com/products/giant-vegeta-super-saiyan-blue-35cm-figure-dragon-ball-collectible"/>
    <title>Giant Vegeta Super Saiyan Blue 35cm Figure – Dragon Ball Collectible</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>Action Nook</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0687/7413/3934/files/B4A8D709-F393-4CE2-8A07-11F6C82946DD.jpg?v=1756999773"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Action Nook<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            599.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span>Power up your collection with this Giant Vegeta Super Saiyan Blue 35cm Figure! ⚡</span></p>
<p><span>Standing tall at 35 cm, this figure showcases Vegeta in his fierce Super Saiyan Blue form with incredible detailing and dynamic posture. A true masterpiece for every Dragon Ball fan!</span></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span>✔️ Massive 35 cm size – perfect centerpiece</span></p>
<p><span>✔️ High-quality sculpt with sharp details</span></p>
<p><span>✔️ Sturdy base for display stability</span></p>
<p><span>✔️ Must-have for Dragon Ball Z / Super collectors</span></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span>Bring the Prince of Saiyans home and let him guard your collection with pride! 👑🔥</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8826868826286</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="INR">599.00</s:price>
      <s:sku/>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8826508312750</id>
    <published>2025-09-04T15:35:17+05:30</published>
    <updated>2025-09-04T15:35:17+05:30</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://actionnook.com/products/dragon-ball-gt-super-saiyan-4-goku-30cm-action-figure-anime-collectible-statue-with-dragon-ball"/>
    <title>Dragon Ball GT Super Saiyan 4 Goku 30cm Action Figure – Anime Collectible Statue with Dragon Ball</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>Action Nook</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0687/7413/3934/files/A6E91D41-5D65-43B2-8C1A-24FEC473EAD8.jpg?v=1756979952"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Action Nook<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            1099.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><span>Bring the power of Dragon Ball GT to your collection with this 30cm Super Saiyan 4 Goku action figure. Standing tall with incredible detail, this collectible captures Goku in his legendary SSJ4 form – complete with his red fur, sharp hair spikes, flowing tail, and intense expression. The figure also includes a Dragon Ball accessory, making it a must-have piece for fans and collectors alike.</span></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span>Crafted from high-quality PVC material, this anime statue is both durable and eye-catching, perfect for display on your shelf, desk, or collector’s showcase. A true centerpiece for Dragon Ball fans, anime lovers, and action figure enthusiasts, this Goku figure makes an unforgettable gift or a prized addition to your collection.</span></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span>⚡ Add Super Saiyan 4 Goku 30cm figure to your Dragon Ball universe today!</span></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8826508312750</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="INR">1099.00</s:price>
      <s:sku/>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8814708654254</id>
    <published>2025-08-20T23:25:24+05:30</published>
    <updated>2025-08-20T23:25:24+05:30</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://actionnook.com/products/dragon-ball-super-super-saiyan-blue-evolved-vegeta-figure-18cm-anime-statue"/>
    <title>Dragon Ball Super Super Saiyan Blue Evolved Vegeta Figure - 18cm Anime Statue</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>Action Nook</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0687/7413/3934/files/D66109A0-FE83-4FDE-AC51-30F8F06FC259.jpg?v=1755712396"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Action Nook<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            599.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Showcase the ultimate evolution of the Saiyan Prince with this dynamic 18cm figure of Super Saiyan Blue Evolved Vegeta! This statue captures Vegeta's most refined and powerful form from Dragon Ball Super, with a confident, mid-flight pose that radiates supreme power.<br>The figure features his iconic blue spiky hair and battle-damaged Saiyan armor, with a torn jumpsuit revealing his muscular form. The sculpted pink and purple flame effects around his body represent the immense power and control of this unique transformation. Mounted on a clear stand, the figure appears to be hovering, ready for a decisive strike.<br>Key Features:<br> * Elite Detail: Faithfully recreated to show every aspect of Vegeta's Super Saiyan Blue Evolved form, from the distinct hair to the battle damage on his clothes.<br> * Compact &amp; Dynamic: At 18cm, it's the perfect size for display, with a mid-air pose that adds a sense of action and energy to your collection.<br> * Translucent Effects: The sculpted aura effects in a pink-purple hue bring a unique and powerful visual element to the figure.<br> * High-Quality Build: Made from durable PVC for a long-lasting and detailed finish.<br> * Collector's Gem: An essential piece for any Dragon Ball Super fan, celebrating Vegeta's ultimate display of pride and strength.<br>Add the Prince of All Saiyans in his most evolved form to your home. This Super Saiyan Blue Evolved Vegeta figure is a perfect tribute to his character and a fantastic centerpiece for any fan's display.</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8814708654254</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="INR">599.00</s:price>
      <s:sku/>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8814706688174</id>
    <published>2025-08-20T23:21:37+05:30</published>
    <updated>2025-08-20T23:21:37+05:30</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://actionnook.com/products/dragon-ball-z-super-saiyan-vegeta-figure-30cm-final-flash-statue"/>
    <title>Dragon Ball Z Super Saiyan Vegeta Figure - 30cm Final Flash Statue</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>Action Nook</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0687/7413/3934/files/2C8A612F-BDD8-4B6B-9FF9-84EAFB84E85C.jpg?v=1755712246"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Action Nook<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            899.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Unleash the power of the Saiyan Prince with this incredibly detailed 30cm figure of Super Saiyan Vegeta! This dynamic statue captures the intensity and rage of Vegeta at his peak, with a pose that radiates raw power and determination.<br>The figure showcases Vegeta in his iconic battle-damaged Saiyan armor, with a torn blue jumpsuit revealing his chiseled physique. The sculpted lightning effects around his body and at his feet symbolize the immense energy of his Super Saiyan form, making this a truly electrifying piece. His enraged expression, battle scars, and torn gloves all contribute to an authentic and powerful representation of the character.<br>Key Features:<br> * Intense Detail: Meticulously sculpted to show every aspect of Vegeta's battle-worn state, from the rips in his clothes to the scowl on his face.<br> * Massive Scale: Standing at a substantial 30cm, this figure makes a bold statement and is the perfect centerpiece for any collection.<br> * Dynamic Effects: Features translucent, sculpted lightning bolts that bring his Super Saiyan power to life, creating a sense of action and energy.<br> * High-Quality Materials: Made from durable PVC, ensuring a long-lasting and high-quality finish.<br> * Essential Collector's Piece: A must-have for every Dragon Ball Z fan and collector, celebrating one of the series' most legendary and iconic characters.<br>Bring the Prince of All Saiyans to your home and display his unyielding pride and power. This Super Saiyan Vegeta figure is a perfect tribute to his character and a fantastic addition to any anime collection.</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8814706688174</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="INR">899.00</s:price>
      <s:sku/>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8781798473902</id>
    <published>2025-06-28T16:06:51+05:30</published>
    <updated>2025-06-28T16:06:51+05:30</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://actionnook.com/products/beerus-god-of-destruction-figure-dragon-ball-super-collectible-30cm"/>
    <title>Beerus God of Destruction Figure - Dragon Ball Super Collectible (30CM)</title>
    <s:type>actiion figure</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Action Nook</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0687/7413/3934/files/IMG_7793.jpg?v=1751106982"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Action Nook<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>actiion figure<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            699.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Command respect with this imposing <b>30CM tall</b> Beerus, the God of Destruction, figure from Dragon Ball Super! This highly detailed collectible perfectly captures Beerus in his iconic relaxed yet powerful pose, showcasing his lean, feline physique and distinctive attire.</p>
<p>Every intricate detail is meticulously sculpted, from Beerus's unique head shape and piercing eyes to his gold wristbands, blue and black diamond-patterned clothing, and flowing sash. The dynamic base, depicting a rocky, destroyed landscape, adds to the aura of his destructive power and authority. This premium figure is an absolute must-have for any dedicated Dragon Ball Super fan who appreciates the series' most powerful and charismatic deities.</p>
<p>Crafted from high-quality, durable PVC materials, this Beerus figure is an excellent centerpiece for any display shelf, desk, or anime collection. It embodies the supreme power and aloof nature of a God of Destruction. Ideal for gifting or personal enjoyment, it's a powerful tribute to one of the Dragon Ball universe's most influential characters.</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>30cm figure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>action figure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>anime merchandise</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Beerus collectible</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Beerus figure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>character statue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>collectible statue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>DBZ figure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>DBZ villain</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Destroyer God</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Dragon Ball merchandise</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Dragon Ball Super</s:tag>
    <s:tag>God of Destruction</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Lord Beerus</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Super Saiyan God</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Universe 7</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Whis</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8781798473902</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="INR">699.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>300</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8781454770350</id>
    <published>2025-06-28T11:54:21+05:30</published>
    <updated>2025-06-28T11:54:21+05:30</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://actionnook.com/products/goku-ultra-instinct-omen-battle-damaged-figure-dragon-ball-super-collectible-24cm"/>
    <title>Goku Ultra Instinct Omen Battle-Damaged Figure - Dragon Ball Super Collectible (24CM)</title>
    <s:type>actiion figure</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Action Nook</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0687/7413/3934/files/IMG_7770.jpg?v=1751091753"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Action Nook<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>actiion figure<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            799.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Relive the epic battles of Dragon Ball Super with this powerful <b>24CM tall</b> Goku Ultra Instinct Omen Battle-Damaged figure! This highly detailed collectible captures Goku in his raw, instinctual form before mastering Ultra Instinct, showcasing his tattered gi, visible battle scars, and surrounded by dynamic pink energy effects.</p>
<p>Every muscle and contour is meticulously sculpted, highlighting Goku's intense determination and raw power. His iconic spiky black hair stands tall, and the translucent pink aura gives the impression of his surging power. Mounted on a clear stand, the figure appears to float in mid-air, ready for the next clash. This premium figure is a must-have for any dedicated Dragon Ball Super fan who cherishes the intense moments of the Tournament of Power.</p>
<p>Crafted from high-quality, durable PVC materials, this Goku Ultra Instinct Omen figure is an excellent addition to any display shelf, desk, or anime collection. It embodies the relentless fighting spirit and unbreakable will of Son Goku. Ideal for gifting or personal enjoyment, it's a powerful tribute to one of anime's greatest heroes.</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>24cm figure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>action figure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>anime merchandise</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Battle Damaged Goku</s:tag>
    <s:tag>character statue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>collectible statue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>DBZ collectible</s:tag>
    <s:tag>DBZ figure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Dragon Ball merchandise</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Dragon Ball Super</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Goku collectible</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Goku figure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Instinct Goku</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Omen Goku</s:tag>
    <s:tag>premium figure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Son Goku</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Tournament of Power</s:tag>
    <s:tag>UI Omen</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Ultra Instinct Omen</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8781454770350</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="INR">799.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>300</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8781379567790</id>
    <published>2025-06-28T10:47:02+05:30</published>
    <updated>2025-06-28T10:47:02+05:30</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://actionnook.com/products/goku-ultra-instinct-awakened-figure-dragon-ball-super-collectible-22cm"/>
    <title>Goku Ultra Instinct Awakened Figure - Dragon Ball Super Collectible (22CM)</title>
    <s:type>actiion figure</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Action Nook</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0687/7413/3934/files/IMG_7803.jpg?v=1751087760"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Action Nook<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>actiion figure<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            799.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Harness the ultimate power of the Gods with this breathtaking <b>22CM tall</b> Goku Ultra Instinct Awakened figure! This highly detailed collectible perfectly captures Goku in his most powerful form, Ultra Instinct, showcasing his signature silver hair, calm yet determined expression, and the dynamic pink/red aura effects signifying his perfected autonomous movements.</p>
<p>Every muscle and contour is meticulously sculpted, from Goku's defined physique to the battle-worn orange gi. The translucent pink energy surrounding him adds to the aura of raw power and speed. Mounted on a clear base, this premium figure appears to float, ready to unleash devastating attacks.</p>
<p>Crafted from high-quality, durable PVC materials, this Goku Ultra Instinct figure is an absolute must-have for any dedicated Dragon Ball Super fan or anime collector. It will undoubtedly be a majestic centerpiece in your display, radiating the unparalleled strength of a true martial arts master. Ideal for gifting or personal enjoyment, it's a powerful tribute to Goku's ultimate evolution.</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>22cm figure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>action figure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>anime merchandise</s:tag>
    <s:tag>autonomous movement</s:tag>
    <s:tag>character statue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>collectible statue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>DBZ collectible</s:tag>
    <s:tag>DBZ figure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Dragon Ball merchandise</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Dragon Ball Super</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Goku collectible</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Goku Ultra Instinct</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Mastered Ultra Instinct</s:tag>
    <s:tag>premium figure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>silver hair Goku</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Son Goku</s:tag>
    <s:tag>UI Awakened</s:tag>
    <s:tag>UI Goku</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8781379567790</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="INR">799.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>200</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8780579373230</id>
    <published>2025-06-27T21:45:50+05:30</published>
    <updated>2025-06-27T21:45:50+05:30</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://actionnook.com/products/goku-super-saiyan-blue-kaioken-figure-dragon-ball-super-collectible-19cm"/>
    <title>Goku Super Saiyan Blue Kaioken Figure - Dragon Ball Super Collectible (19CM)</title>
    <s:type>actiion figure</s:type>
    <s:vendor>Action Nook</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0687/7413/3934/files/IMG_7815.jpg?v=1751040771"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>Action Nook<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong>actiion figure<br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            459.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p>Unleash the power of a Saiyan God with this dynamic <b>19CM tall</b> Super Saiyan Blue Goku figure! Captured in an iconic battle pose, this highly detailed collectible showcases Goku in his fierce Super Saiyan Blue (SSB) form, radiating immense power, potentially combined with Kaioken as indicated by his intense expression and stance.</p>
<p>Every detail is meticulously sculpted, from Goku's spiky blue hair and determined facial expression to the ripped blue gi top and battle-damaged orange pants. This premium figure perfectly encapsulates the raw power and intensity of Dragon Ball Super's most formidable hero.</p>
<p>Crafted from high-quality, durable PVC, this Goku SSB figure is a must-have for any Dragon Ball Z or Dragon Ball Super fan. It's an excellent addition to any display shelf, desk, or anime collection, making a powerful statement. Ideal for gifting or personal enjoyment, it embodies the spirit of unrelenting power and determination.</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>action figure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>anime merchandise</s:tag>
    <s:tag>character statue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>collectible statue</s:tag>
    <s:tag>DBZ collectible</s:tag>
    <s:tag>DBZ figure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Dragon Ball merchandise</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Dragon Ball Super</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Goku collectible</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Goku figure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Goku Kaioken</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Kaioken</s:tag>
    <s:tag>premium figure</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Saiyan God</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Son Goku</s:tag>
    <s:tag>SSB Goku</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Super Saiyan Blue</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://actionnook.com/products/8780579373230</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="INR">459.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>250</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
